Oh did you want me to go away and you
can go home and have a night off?
No that's absolutely fine, if you're
fine with it then I'm absolutely fine.
Oh I'm fine with it. Okay so um uh
yeah
this is you can write a book, I'm Mark
Stringer and
um a friend of mine who's written at
least a dozen
books uh during the pandemic he ran a
course
online on how to write non -fiction
books and one of the things I remember
from
that course, it was a very good
course, was that when you're doing a
non -fiction
book you should answer at least these
four questions.
Why me? Why you? Why this?
And why now? So um I'm going to answer
those questions as
an introduction uh so why me?
So why me is because I wrote a book.
Thank you. It's called Delivering the
Impossible and it's a book about
project
management.